NATALIIA DASHKO QA Engineer

CONTACT INFO

Location: Kyiv, Ukraine

Phone: +380982255114 (viber, telegram) e-mail: dashkonataliia@gmail.com

nataliya77@i.ua

linkedin: https://www.linkedin.com/in/nataliiadashko/

OBJECTIVE

Getting a position of QA Engineer.

SUMMARY

I have a mathematics education and experience in testing websites and mobile applications. I have a good theoretical knowledge base and practical skills in preparing test cases (TestRail), preparing bug reports (Jira, GitLab). I have experience in using SQL, HTML, CSS. I really want to move further into automation. I am the motivated and development-oriented person who sees himself as a member of a self-sufficient team. I hope that with my participation the team will make effective decisions to assess the quality of a software product and write optimal test cases. This will serve to create a quality product. In teamwork, I value relationships, personal qualities and professionalism.

SKILLS

- Knowledge of testing theory, testing types and test design techniques
- Understanding of SDLC/STLC, Bug Life Cycle
- Understanding of testing methodologies
- Experience in Web testing/ Mobile Testing
- Experience in Dev tools (Chrome dev tools etc.)
- Experience with bug reporting tool (JIRA, GitLab)
- Experience in designing test documentation (Check-lists, Test Cases, Bug reports)
- Experience with a test management tool (TestRail)
- Knowledge of HTML, CSS, SQL
- Understanding of CI/CD concepts
- Understanding of client-server architecture
- Understanding of networking (TCP/IP, DNS protocols, HTTP etc.)
- Experience in API testing (Postman)
- Base knowledge of Java

EXPERIENCE

Dates: 2021

Responsibilities: 4 months of non-commercial experience in QA/QC: experience in designing test documentation (TestRail), Web and Mobile Testing (Functional and Non-Functional Testing, UI/UX Testing, Manual Testing, Exploratory Testing, Stability/Reliability Testing, Installation Testing, Localization Testing, Failover and Recovery Testing, Configuration Testing, α -Testing), designing test documentation (Check-lists, Test Cases, Bug reports) and bug reports (GitLab)

Position: Trainee QA Engineer

Company: SkillUp and Test Team Now

Dates: 2018-2021

Responsibilities: acceptance α -testing of website, Functional and Non-Functional Testing, UI/UX Testing, Manual Testing, Exploratory Testing, Localization Testing, maintenance of web-site; experience in Mobile testing, designing test documentation (Check-lists, Test Cases, Bug reports) and bug reports (JIRA)

Position: Trainee QA Engineer Company: Genesa publishing house



• Dates: 2005-2021

Responsibilities: selection and implementation of projects, search for authors of projects, preparation of contracts, quality control of projects at all stages of creation

Position: Head of Physics and Mathematics Department and lead editor

Company: Genesa publishing house

• Dates: 2000-2005

Responsibilities: teaching mathematics and computer science *Position*: teacher of mathematics and computer science

Company: School of Kyiv

EDUCATION

• 1995-2000

University: Kyiv National Taras Shevchenko University *Department (Specialization)*: Mathematician, teacher

Degree: Specialist

CERTIFICATIONS

• 2021

SkillUp educational center of IT specialists Quality Assurance Certificate

• 2021

Sololearn educational platform of IT specialists HTML Certificate – SQL Certificate – CSS Certificate

LANGUAGES

Ukrainian (native), Russian (native), English (intermediate)

ADDITIONAL INFO

I love sports, mountains, sea, reading books, theater, walking in the wood, picking mushrooms, roller-skate ☺